[Music]
I was just vibing to the music. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. The music is not bad. How
are you doing, Kim? I'm doing okay. How
are you? Yes. All good. All good. Thank
you so much uh for joining uh on this
super cool uh conference. Uh, may I ask
where are you calling us from? I'm out
of Atlanta right now. Born in Trinidad,
grew up in New York. Um, been in Atlanta
for a few years. Fantastic. Fantastic.
Um, well um
uh this is just a little explanation by
the way because this uh section is going
to be definitely an interesting one. So
um Kimu is going to do some uh live vibe
coding building in front of us. uh and
there will be a section where we jump
into the next talk because in the
background uh there will be the build
that Kim we will come back to uh with us
uh right after the next section I don't
know if that made too much sense I might
not need to you might not need to okay
need to but let's see what happens
because we don't Okay good good okay
good with agents you never know
absolutely absolutely um Cool. Well,
then uh the floor is yours. So, can we
Thank you. So, I want to start out with
a prompt that I'm going to use to VIP
code. Um let's bring it
up. And uh here it is. And it reads,
"You're an expert brand, storyteller,
and copywriter for an innovative AI
products. Write a compelling and
personable homepage introduction for a
new agent called Cover AI." Sounds
interesting.
The the agent image is attached. Its
purpose and workflow are detailed in the
read me. Tone and style. Friendly,
confident, and lovable. Clean and
helpful with a spark of delight.
Emphasis on real world value and how it
makes life easier. Go. Craft a homepage
blurb instantly that connects with
visitors, explains what cover AI does,
and invites them to explore. I'm
actually going to paste this prompt. And
the only context that I'm giving to this
prompt is my mermaid diagram which is
marked up in um this markdown here which
in essence shows a
flowchart of uh what's going on here. So
uh call to action encourage users to try
cover AI or learn how it works. All
right, let's copy this bad
boy. All right, let's head over to
lovable. Okay, let's paste you
in and let's hit enter. Okay, while
lovable turns away, let's talk a little
bit more about what coveri actually is.
So, um let's head over to the GitHub
repo. Not that one, not that one, but
this one. And this was put together by a
colleague at um agency
services um by the name of Tyrese Dixon.
Um he's a young technologist up and
coming. Let's bring up his LinkedIn
because let's give him some shine. He
worked really hard on this guy. So, you
know, let's give him some
shine.
Ty. Oh, wait. He was just there. Okay,
here he is. Uh, he's he's based in New
York, right? And yeah, he's he interns
here with us. All
right, so he put together this read me
which kind of describes what lovable
generating for me, right? Let's take a
look at it. And it's based on his
documentation. So let's see if it gets
it
right. So uh, coverage AI agent
prerequisites. Okay, what do I need? I
need I need Dagger. I need to go to
Dagger and
install Dagger at version 185. Okay, I
already have Dagger, so need no need for
that. How do I configure this thing?
Okay, all repos should be configured to
run and generate coverage reports. H
okay. Uh okay, I can I think I have that
configured to create an output file with
the test results in a JSON format. Okay,
and it takes this configuration. All
right, simple enough. Looks like the
commits are going to have this AI gen
thing. Um, I have just configured. Okay,
this the command to render the coverage
report. And this is what the output JSON
is going to be. So, it just kind of
wants to know how like my coverage
report set up. Interesting. Uh, I can
limit it to one file at a time. Uh,
iterations doesn't matter. I know
because I built it.
So let's skip over that. It needs to
know how my tests are saved. Do do you
want to save your tests that are
generated next to the code under test? I
do. All right. This kind of gives a
brief description on what what these
properties are. Let's keep it moving. So
usage. Oh, I need to do this dagger call
thing. Okay. What am I passing into
that? All the branch a GitHub token. The
repository that I want to generate tests
for. This log fire access token all
seems pretty straightforward. Open
router. Hey, this thing integrates with
open router. What is open router? Well,
open router is a unified interface for
LLMs.
very popular amongst the um AI community
because you know it serves as like a
gateway to all things LLM and it has
some really nice features to it too like
access to a ton of models from a ton of
different providers. Let's get back
to Tyrese's documentation. Oh, it also
takes an open Oh, so either or. So I can
provide it open router key or I can
provide it a open API key. Okay, cool.
All right, dagger call. Okay. All right.
This thing's also extensible. So out of
the box, they support Jest and they
support
Piest. All right. So that means all my
JavaScript projects are pretty much
covered in Typescript projects. If I
code in Python, I'm covered. But if I
don't code in any of those two
languages, I can build my own plugin.
Let's let's see what I need to do to
build my own plug-in. I just need to I
just need to
um implement these four functions. Get
code onto test, get the coverage HTML,
get coverage reports, and parsing the
test results. Okay. Can I look at a
sample implementation?
Sure. There's the just
implementation. Makes sense. All right.
Let's go
back. Uh
What else do I need? Oh, let's take a
look at how this thing actually works.
So, here's the agentic workflow. Looks
like there are two agents here. There's
a pull request agent and there's a
coverage agent. Okay, so get code under
test is what the coverage agent does. It
analyzes a coverage report, generates
unit tests, and if it generates a unit
test that then no, then then it runs the
test inside of a container. That's
probably what that dagger thing is for.
Okay. If the test fails, then it will
keep going, keep going until I guess it
decides that, hey, I can't I can't write
this test or I'm successful. And if it's
successful, it looks like it returns a
code module, which sounds like a
structured response. All right, we'll
take a look at that in a second. And
then we have this pull request agent.
Now, for the non-technical folks, pull
requests is how developers introduce
change into a repository. So how we
communicate and talk about change. Well,
we'll take a look at that in a second as
well. Okay. So um add get changes. It
does a commit pushes to the remote
branch. Checks to see if a PR exists
first. If there's no PR, it creates one.
Okay. And then it's done. The PR exists
and it'll update the existing PR. Okay.
So this is so this part here is probably
how the whole process actually works. So
we start the test
generation. We build our test
environment inside of a
container. We get the coverage reports.
We rank them based on percentage because
we really want to tackle the parts of
our application that is getting the
least amount of attention. I guess we
loop through these ranked reports and
then we run the agent to generate
tests. Interesting. Okay. What do we do
from there? Um, we set up a PR container
for the pull request if we're
successful. And then we just run this
agent. So, I guess this agent is calling
that agent, but it's passing in a
container with a test in it. Oh, I like
that. And then we create a PR with the
new test, I guess, for a human being to
look at because, you know, these agents,
they be doing stuff, we don't know what
they doing sometimes. So, got to have a
human in the loop somehow.
But if we generate tests and the tests
fail, we still set up a PR
container and then we generate a pull
request, but we give it a little bit
more context as to well why did you
fail? So maybe the human being can kind
of get a head start as to okay this
thing failed, but what's going on here?
And we also add some comments to kind of
hint that that human being to hey
something has failed here. Let's go back
to logo. I want to tell you guys a
little story how I launched the
um agency services. So I actually
beginning of the year woke up and was
just like you know
what I want I I just I had a really good
year the the year before I published for
um I wrote a blog about technical debt
really passionate about technical debt
and testing and best practices and um I
often find that developers are most
productive when hurdles are removed and
they're able to focus on shipping
features and not much maintaining code
which can sometimes feel like a chore
bog you down sometimes even change your
day when you have a bug uh I'm really
passionate about that so I was like oh I
form a company around that so let's go
up to me when I decided to build this
thing and I started vibe coding now this
thing is broken and I know why and I
explain that for a second because I
broke lovable just
now I'll explain why lovable is broken
we kind of have like a lovehate
relationship lovable and
because it kind of got me off the
ground. But I'm a little bit of more
experienced developer and as you guys
can see from all the talks that we've
heard thus far about vibe coding. It
comes with a byproduct of technical
debt, right? That's that's the byproduct
because you know you're trusting you're
saying I want this in a sentence and
then it goes off and tries to build it
but you don't really know what it's
building. You don't really know what
it's doing. Let me go let me go down.
Let me go down. Let me go down. you go
down to where where where me and Lovable
started to argue. Okay. Yeah. So, here
here we go. You start seeing all these
bill failures because eventually I got
my website up, but Lovable when I
started asking it for more advanced
features, it just started to fall down.
So, my response was, "All right, how
about I hop on the same B branch as
Lovable and start pairing with it. Let
me go all the way to the bottom and and
just start pairing with it. And that's
what I and that's what I started to do.
Um, a little bit of spoilers. You guys
see all these external commits coming in
from cover AI. It's a little spoiler.
What is it doing? It's generating
tests, but lovable doesn't like that
because it wasn't made to generate tests
and check itself. I even asked it if it
could do that right here. Right. I'm
like, "Hey, can you wire up just
Right. So that at least I know once I
reach to a point where I feel like the
functionality is good that you're
actually
working and it refused to do that. So I
did it myself. So let's to go take a
look at
um the longstanding running PR that I
had with Lovable. One second. So, this
is my this is actually my um I'm going
to move this repo eventually, but this
is actually where I keep the source code
for agency services and five days
ago I opened up well cover AI opened up
this pull
request and it started to generate tests
on the same branch that lovable
actually building out my website.
Um, so this is kind of where it started
about 4 days
ago. And let's scroll all the way down
to the bottom where we probably were
going to see lovable, right? Because we
just asked it to update my
homepage. But what I ended up what ended
up happening to me is that
um I had a solution of a website which
you guys can go to. I can kind of put
the I can put the because I want to do
slides last. I'm all about
showing, right? Oops. If you guys want
to go to the website, you can go
now. Let me put it up. So, you can scan
it over here and go to it, right, and
take a look at it.
But what I ended up at the end of the
day was a code base that I knew nothing
about and that when it broke it was very
hard to debug. Um
so after creating that those two
agents and hold
on yeah running test and setting up my
repo to actually create a coverage
report. I was able
to generate let's see how many tests I
was able to generate. It basically
validated everything that level was
doing for me actually worked is all unit
tests. Let's
see. Oh, we got some failing tests. Of
course, we got some feeling tests
because we just asked for new
functionality. But at least we get to
see what
worked, right? Because these were these
were all passing right before this. And
I could show you guys actually.
Um, see, I had I had 95%
coverage before I asked for that new
feature and everything was covered. Um,
uh, the the only file that was kind of
lacking coverage is this one right here,
which is at
78%. And this kind of blew me away. I've
never been able to get these types of
numbers from an agent doing this before.
I've done this type of agent and project
several times. I think I've rebuilt this
at least seven times. Um, and I'm going
to show you guys how it was done in just
a sec. So, hold on to your seats. Let's
go back to my
terminal. So, okay. Okay, so I have
what
351 passing
tests. Um, that validates that at
least
350 test 351 test cases still work from
the new feature that I asked level for
for right now. I am going to kick off my
agent in just a sec, but I don't know if
I'm going to run out of time. So, I'm
going to kick it off. See if I can get
coverage for this. Right. Actually, no.
Wait a minute. This is the existing
test. So, this broke. Let me do a get
pull. So, that means that change
actually broke some functionality.
That's what this means. My menu bars
broke. I pulled this pulled on the new
changes. Let me run my test
again. Run my test
again. My goal for this talk is actually
to launch this by the end of the talk.
So, let's see what happens. Let me pull
down it. Pull it down
again. Let's see what's
broken. Oh, no. All passing tests. Okay.
Well, let's let's launch the
application.
Run dev. I can't even trust what Lovel
tells me at this point because it's
really not configured to work with
[Music]
um Hold on. Am I on the right
branch? Yes, I
[Music]
am. Well done. See, live demo is
dangerous. Let's see.
I don't
see. Maybe it's because of that broken
T. I don't see that change. Let me see
what's going on over
[Music]
here. Let's see what's going on over
here. I don't see the change.
Did it just not do
it? Oh
boy. Live
demos. All right, I'm going to segue for
a second just so you guys can see how
this agent works and how it was built.
Okay, we'll come back to this. Like I
said, the chance is not wasn't going to
work. All right, but let's take a look
at daggers tracing to see what happened
um for some previous runs that I've
done. Well, how I got to 551 passing
tests. Let's take a close
look. So, we have this generate unit
test function. This was ran on Mother's
Day, by the way. So let's see how these
agents think and how it was coded to
work when it when it is
working.
Okay, generate unit test. All right,
just some logging information here. So
it looks like we're standing up three
agents. One of these agents actually got
fired during the creation of this which
is this review agent because it was just
it didn't really serve a purpose and it
was just kind of burning burning tokens.
So you're not going to
see even though it's there in the logs
you're not going to see any anything
from that. So we have a coverai agent
that is generating tests for our
navigation menu file.
It's finished the generation and I I am
using a structural response because
remember we get back a code module. So
the code module that we get back we have
an actual strategy. The strategy is kind
of interesting because the strategy
gives me a peak as to into the model's
mind as to what it was thinking when it
was generating the test in terms of the
strategy that it's trying to use to
increase coverage.
Then we get the actual code that it
tries to generate and then if it runs
the code consecutively iteratively in
the container and it finds any errors
it'll put it in this field here. So
let's scroll all the way down because
this is almost like a summary of what's
going on and let's scroll all the way
down to where where this agent's act
where the agent was actually running and
trying to build that test. So here we
are and remember this is all extensible.
So this reporter is working with
justest. So when we click on reporter
um the reporter grabs the coverage
html and again it's using this just
plugin right and it has access to a
container right we load in the
package.json because we want to
understand the
dependencies okay and let's see what the
first thing that the agent does. agent
runs and the very first thing it does is
generates a test. This was on the 11th,
so it was a few days ago. Okay, so it
generates a test. So it wants to see if
that test has any errors. So it actually
executes the the command inside of the
container to run the test and get
feedback from that. So let's take a look
at
that. And as you can see, the test
failed because it remember we're
outputting a JSON.
But the reporter also has an has another
function where we can parse it. So we
can get like a readable like what
actually happened. So here's the error
to
that. Okay. So then I'm going to keep
going and it kept going. It kept going.
It kept generating. It kept going.
There's no need for us to look at that.
So eventually it generated a passing
test because when it ran the coverage
report and it tried to parse the
results, there's no error here. So now
that has a passing test, it sends that
passing test to the next agent and
that's our pull request agent. So let's
take a look at our pull request agent
and see what what it's actually doing.
Okay,
reporter. All right, looking at the
coverage. So the first thing that the
pull request agent is going to do inside
of this container is check the get
status to see if there's anything and it
does. It finds a new file and that's
this generated na navigation context
menu file
right and it's just like okay well let
me add that it's adds
it and then it creates a commit message
cover AI adds test for navigation menu
to improve coverage from 0%. because we
don't get that
relable. Um, and then we Yep. Um, thank
you so much for like showing us how far
this can go in such a short amount of
time.
We are trying to wrap up with um like uh
we are trying to bridge with our our
next next speaker. Okay, that said, I
just want to say massive kudos on taking
it this far because like again super
short amount of time and I really love
like the focus you're having on
testdriven development. I think you know
like you had the the perfect I mean this
is our thesis right AI native
development like everything should be
like test driven and the fact that
lovable and all these uh platforms right
now don't have this is um an area of of
improvement. So, and I wanted also to
thank you for showing like the community
uh kind of like how to go about it like
how to debug, what are the issues, how
how you go about your your workflow. Um
so really really appreciate it. Uh
please do share uh some of the links
that you've shared in the chat. I'm sure
a lot of people are going to be really
excited to to take a look at it. But in
that in like that said really really
interesting uh to have had you on the
conference and yeah just wanted to say a
huge huge thank you like that was really
insightful. All right thank you for
having me. Yeah, of course. Thank you.